Like most of Canada, Vancouver and its area is extremely safe
대부분의 캐나다 도시처럼 밴쿠버는 상당히 안전하고
Violent crimes are rare. However, like any large urban city
범죄는 흔치 않지만 큰 도시에서 종종있는
petty crimes are common
작은 범죄는 존재할 수 있습니다
Areas such as downtown east side of Hasting street
다운타운 동쪽 및 East Hasting Street 같은 곳은
are to be avoided walking late at night.
밤늦게 다니는 것을 피하도록 요구됩니다
Transportation and taxis are generally very safe in Vancouver
밴쿠버 대중교통 및 택시는 일반적으로 굉장히 안전하고
and there are many apps used for navigating the cities.
도시를 돌아다니기 위해 만들어진 앱 또한 많습니다
Students have many opportunities to familiarize themselves with Vancouver before exploring on their own
학생은 스스로 밴쿠버를 탐험해보기 전 응급치료 자격증을 가진
as many of our weekend activities are held in and around the city
스텝들이 이끄는 도심 속 주말 액티비티를 통해
led by our first-aid trained staff.
밴쿠버를 알아갈 수 있는 기회를 많이 갖습니다
Bodwell High School is located in the city of North Vancouver
보드웰 하이스쿨은 다운타운을 건넌 북쪽
just across the water on the north side of downtown.
노스밴쿠버에 위치하고 있습니다
North Vancouver is accessible from downtown by the seabus
다운타운에서 노스밴쿠버를 가려면 수상 버스를 타거나
or by crossing the Lion's Gate bridge
Lion’s Gate 다리를 건너야 합니다
It is in a quiet neighbourhood at a roundabout corner
조용한 동네의 회전교차로 끝자락에 위치한 보드웰의 뒤편에는
with a pedestrian trail running along a sea wall at the back of the school
방파제를 따라 보행자를 위한 길이 놓여 있습니다
Students have their own free time after classes and clubs before their study hall and on weekends
학생은 수업과 클럽 활동이 끝난 자습 시간 전, 주말동안 개인 시간을 갖습니다
They are free to go out and explore
그 시간 동안은 학교 밖에 나가도 좋으나
but we ask them to swipe their key FOBs when they leave and return to the school
학교 출입시에는 개인 카드를 긁도록 하고 있어서
so staff is aware of their whereabouts.
스텝들이 학생의 외출여부를 알 수 있도록 합니다
For their safety outside the school, we conduct workshops
외출시 학생의 안전을 위한 워크샵을 통해
to ensure they are aware how to avoid danger
위험한 상황에서 벗어나는 법을 가르치고
and what to do in the case of getting lost.
길을 잃었을 때 어떻게 해야하는지 가르칩니다
Students can call the school anytime - we are reachable 24 hours a day-
24시간 동안 학생은 학교로 언제든 전화할 수 있습니다
use Google Maps, get a taxi,  or simply ask around
구글맵을 쓰거나 택시를 타고, 대부분 캐내디언은
Canadians are generally very kind and willing to assist.
친절하기 때문에 길을 물어서 도움을 청할 수 있습니다
Students should exercise common sense when outside the school
학생은 외출시에 상식을 발휘해서
and not hesitate to call 911 if they find themselves in a dangerous or emergency situation.
위험한 상황에 처하거나 긴급 상황일 경우 911에 전화해야 합니다
Notifying friends or staff when leaving the campus is a good habit for students
외출시 친구나 스텝에게 행선지를 얘기하는 것은 좋은 습관입니다
At night, we require every student to follow curfew
저녁에는 학생들이 안전을 위해 귀가 시간을 따라서
and be back to their boarding by specific times for their safety
정해진 시간까지 기숙사로 돌아오도록 하고 있습니다
All new students are assigned a locker
모든 학생에게는 개인 보관함이 지급되어
where they can put away or lock their valuables or personal items
학생은 귀중품 및 개인 물건을 보관할 수 있습니다
It is not safe to leave valuables out in the open or in common areas
귀중품을 아무데나 또는 공공장소에 놓는 것은 좋지 않습니다
During your child's stay here, they may get a bike, skateboard, rollerblade or other large equipment
학생이 자전거, 스케이트보드, 롤러브레이드 등 큰 장비를 구입하면
The school has safe storage for these items
학교에는 이런 것들을 보관할 수 있는 공간이 마련되어 있습니다
We also require them to adhere to the city's by-laws
또한 학생이 자전거를 탈때 헬맷을 쓰는 등
such as wearing a helmet while riding their bicycles and following traffic laws.
시규정을 잘 지키고 교통 법규를 잘 지키도록 교육하고 있습니다
School staff is here to assist your child in creating a safe, successful, memorable life here at Bodwell.
보드웰 스텝은 학생의 안전하고 기억에 남는 성공적인 생활을 위해 옆에 있습니다